<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RaleighTourGuide</string>
    <string name="hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="entertainment">Entertainment</string>
    <string name="landmarks">Landmarks</string>
    <string name="emergency">Emergency</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


    <!-- Establishment Names -->
    <string name="buku">Buku Raleigh</string>
    <string name="davidsDumplings">David\'s Dumplings</string>
    <string name="sushiBlues">Sushi Blues</string>
    <string name="hotel_sheraton">Sheraton Raleigh Hotel</string>
    <string name="hotel_holidaydowntown">Holiday Inn Raleigh Downtown</string>
    <string name="hotel_marriottcitycenter">Raleigh Marriott City Center</string>



    <!-- Establishment Descriptions -->

    <string name="description_rest_buku">
        Located at the corner of Wilmington and Davie Street, bu•ku: Global Street Food is a local establishment telling a global story. Inspired by the pushcarts of street vendors in cities across the globe, we harvest an array of unique and distinct flavors and present them authentically in a virtual kaleidoscope of plates. The common link being, these are foods that people love.
    </string>
    <string name="description_rest_davidsDumplings">
        This unique eatery is owned and operated by Chef David Mao, a successful establishment owner and culinary innovator in Raleigh since 1976. Over the years, if you have eaten at the Mandarin House, The Abacus, The Great Mall of China, The China Cafe and Grille and most recently, the Duck and Dumpling, then you have enjoyed David\’s inspired menus.
    </string>
    <string name="description_rest_sushiblues">
        One of the triangle\'s coolest night spots, Sushi Blues Cafe offers some of the best Sushi and Japanese food, along a softly lit blues/jazz atmosphere.
    </string>
    <string name="description_hotel_sheraton">
        Make yourself at home here in Raleigh, in one of our 353 spacious and beautifully appointed guest rooms and suites, each of which features the famous Sheraton Signature Bed. Upgrade to our Club Rooms for exclusive lounge access. Host a successful meeting in our 18,000 square feet of recently updated, contemporary meeting and event space, and make use of our expert planning services.
    </string>

    <string name="description_hotel_holidaydowntown">
        Holiday Inn Raleigh Downtown, located in the heart of the city, where you will find everything. Shopping, dining, entertainment and the arts. You are within easy walking distance to the Raleigh Convention Center, Duke Energy Center for the Performing Arts and five free museums.Located just 13 miles from the Raleigh-Durham International Airport, you\’ll spend less time in traffic and more time doing what you came to Raleigh to do.
    </string>

    <string name="description_hotel_marriottcitycenter">
        The Raleigh Marriott City Center offers an elevated experience for business and leisure travelers alike. Our hotel guests can enjoy spacious, well-designed hotel rooms and suites, a vast array of luxury amenities, and intuitive service. The comforts of home await you here in Raleigh in our thoughtfully appointed hotel rooms; each one features a flat-screen TV, marble bathrooms, an ergonomic work area, and luxury bedding.
    </string>



    <!-- Establishment Phone Numbers -->

    <string name="phoneNumber_rest_buku">919-834-6963</string>
    <string name="phoneNumber_rest_sushiblues">919-664-8061</string>
    <string name="phoneNumber_rest_davidsDumplings">919-239-4536</string>
    <string name="phoneNumber_hotel_sheraton">919-834-9900</string>
    <string name="phoneNumber_hotel_holidaydowntown">919-832-0501</string>
    <string name="phoneNumber_hotel_marriottcitycenter">919-833-1120</string>
    

    <!-- Establishment Addresses -->
    <string name="address_rest_buku">110 E Davie St, Raleigh, NC</string>
    <string name="address_rest_sushiBlues">301 Glenwood Ave, Raleigh NC</string>
    <string name="address_rest_davidsDumplings">1900 Hillsborough St, Raleigh, NC</string>
    <string name="address_hotel_sheraton">421 S Salisbury St, Raleigh, NC</string>
    <string name="address_hotel_holidadowntown">320 Hillsborough St, Raleigh, NC</string>
    <string name="address_hotel_marriottcitycenter">500 Fayetteville St, Raleigh, NC</string>
</resources>
